JYOTI ARYA

(Senior Account Executive)

Female

Email: jyotiarya630@gmail.com Mobile: +91-8587892919

CAREER ASPIRATION

Looking for a challenging position in a professional & dynamic organization, which promises independent responsibilities offers opportunities to make best use of knowledge & skills to further enhance personal knowledge in profession Which also offers high growth prospects.

PROFILE

My career graph has always allowed me to gain valuable experience in various finance and accounts division. Working with corporate and interaction with international client has helped me develop a methodical approach. I greatly value team-dynamics and importance of working as a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

British Council Management (Senior Executive)

Oct 2022-Present

- Maintaining the key service level requirement & KPI targets between SSC and Region.
- Responsible for extracting and analyzing reports from SAP and other sources and responsible for monthly/ Quarterly close process.
- Involve in intercompany PO creation, Journal & bulk request process.
- Preparing Accrual, Recharge & Billing reports for intercompany centralized process.
- Manual adjustments for PO and SO.
- P&L, Vendor, GL & WBS reconciliation.
- Maintaining tracker, email handling & resolving business partners queries.
- Email allocation, producing day end reporting(EOD)

IBM (Account Payable-Subject Matter Expert)

Nov 2021-Sep 2022

- Preparing DTP's
- Handling team of 15 Members.
- Knowledge of T&E Processing.
- Doing clearing up GRIR for inventory invoices, vendor deviation and vendor clearing check through SAPT code.
- Monitoring vendor accounts and Prepayment.
- Approver Ageing Report- Track cases which are pending with the client for resolution.

- Reject Report-To give them foresight about accruals.
- Knowledge of Indian accounting, section 194(Income tax TDS), GST TDS, RCM.
- Training new hires on basic PTP concept and invoice processing.
- Performing audit & daily workflow reconciliation.
- Producing day end reporting (EOD).
- Doing all month end activity, produce monthly reports.

Genpact India Pvt Ltd (Account Payable-Process Developer)

Nov 2019-2021

- Allocating daily responsibility among team members.
- Performing audit & daily workflow reconciliation.
- Producing day end reporting (EOD)
- Motivating the team to achieve high standard and Achieve SLA.
- Responsible for updating specific information from invoices and update (SOP's)
- Producing weekly and monthly SLA reports
- Doing all month end activity, produce monthly report.

Accenture Solution Pvt Ltd (Account Payable-Executive)

May 2017-Oct 2019

- Accurately Process & manage invoices (Non-Po/Po) (Single Payment /Wire Payment).
- VSR (Vendor Statement Reconciliation), Bank Reconciliation.
- Match Exception Resolution/Processing Post Resolution/Resolve invoice Discrepancies.
- Release invoice payment, Perform dispute management, Analysis.
- Doing all month end activity, produce monthly reports.
- Email Resolution and interact with vendor and quick respond to queries.
- Mentoring and training up juniors and new staff.

| ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS | | | |
|-------------------------|-----------|---------------------------------------|------------------|
| Year | Degree | Institute | Per centage/CGPA |
| | | | |
| 2016 | B. Com(H) | Dyal Singh College (Delhi University) | 75% |
| 2013 | XII | Senior Secondary Girls School | 79% |
| 2011 | X | Senior Secondary Girls School | 8.2 |

IT & PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Operating Known: Windows 97,98,2000, Windows professional& windows xp
- Computer Applications: Microsoft word, Microsoft excel, Microsoft PowerPoint.
- Computerized accounting (ERP)
- Software Skill: Tally, Oracle (People Soft 9.2), Oracle (JDE), DMS, SAP.
- Workflow: DFM(Document Flow Manager), Coupa

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- Rewarded by Core value Campion Award-Accenture
- Appreciation by **SBI INTOUCH BRANCH** (Communique 2014-2015)

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY

- Member of **CII-YI YUVA**(360* Leadership program)
- Member of **UMEED** (A Drop of hope)

LANGUAGES KNOWN

- English
- Hindi

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality : Indian

• Address : 1280/8, Comman Area Govindpuri, Kalkaji, South Delhi, New Delhi - 110019